A Guide to the Papers of the Prince Edward County Free School 1963-1967
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Office of Pupil Personnel
  - Correspondence
    - Check Out Sheets (Box-folder 35:4)
    - Grade Placement (Box-folder 35:5)
    - Memo's from Dudley (Box-folder 35:6)
    - Correspondence, Absence Reports, etc (Box-folder 35:7)
    - Correspondence-Arthur Dudley Pupil Personnel Director (Box-folder 35:8)
    - Otis Scores (Box-folder 35:9)
    - Travel Requisition (Box-folder 35:10)
    - The Virginia Retirement System Oct 1963- Dec (Box-folder 35:11)
    - Virginia Retirement System (Box-folder 35:12)
    - Virginia Retirement System (Box-folder 35:13)
    - The Virginia Supplement Retirement System Sept 1963 (Box-folder 35:14)
  - Lunch Daily Reports
    - Application For Secondary Data Sheets (Box-folder 36:1)
    - Form Fo-5 Monthly Summary Sheets for Cafeteria Programs (Box-folder 36:2)
    - Cafeteria Daily Reports 4-13-1964 (Box-folder 36:3)
    - Inventory (Box-folder 36:4)
    - Menu's (Box-folder 36:5)
    - National School Lunch Program and Special Milk Program Information (Box-folder 36:6)
    - Week of September 16th-20th (Box-folder 36:7)
    - Monday Sept 3rd, 1963 (Box-folder 36:8)
    - Tuesday Sept 24th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:9)
    - Wednesday Sept 25th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:10)
    - Thursday Sept 26th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:11)
    - Friday Sept 27th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:12)
    - Monday Sept 30th, 9163 (Box-folder 36:13)
    - Tuesday October 1st, 1963 (Box-folder 36:14)
    - Wednesday October 2nd, 1963 (Box-folder 36:15)
    - Thursday October 3rd, 1963 (Box-folder 36:16)
    - Friday October 4th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:17)
    - Monday October 7th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:18)
    - Tuesday October 8th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:19)
    - Wednesday October 9th 1963 (Box-folder 36:20)
    - Thursday October 10th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:21)
    - Friday Oct 11th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:22)
    - Monday October 14th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:23)
    - Tuesday October 15th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:24)
    - Wednesday October 16th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:25)
    - Thursday October 17th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:26)
    - Friday October 18th, 1963 (Box-folder 36:27)
    - Monday October 21, 1963 (Box-folder 37:1)
    - Tuesday October 22, 1963 (Box-folder 37:2)
    - Wednesday October 23rd, 1964 (Box-folder 37:3)
    - Thursday October 24th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:4)
    - Friday October 25th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:5)
    - Monday October 26th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:6)
    - Tuesday October 29th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:7)
    - Wednesday October 30th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:8)
    - Thursday October 31st, 1963 (Box-folder 37:9)
    - Monday Nov 4th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:10)
    - Tuesday Nov 5th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:11)
    - Wednesday Nov 6th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:12)
    - Thursday Nov 7th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:13)
    - Friday Nov 8th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:14)
    - Monday Nov 11th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:15)
    - Tuesday Nov 12th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:16)
    - Wednesday Nov 13th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:17)
    - Thursday Nov 14th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:18)
    - Friday Nov 15th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:19)
    - Monday Nov 18th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:20)
    - Tuesday Nov 19th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:21)
    - Wednesday Nov 20th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:22)
    - Thursday Nov 21st, 1963 (Box-folder 37:23)
    - Friday Nov 22nd, 1963 (Box-folder 37:24)
    - Tuesday Nov 26th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:25)
    - Monday Dec 2nd, 1963 (Box-folder 37:26)
    - Tuesday Dec 3rd, 1963 (Box-folder 37:27)
    - Wednesday Dec 4th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:28)
    - Thursday Dec 5th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:29)
    - Friday Dec 6th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:30)
    - Monday Dec 9th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:31)
    - Tuesday Dec 10th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:32)
    - Wednesday Dec 11th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:33)
    - Thursday Dec 12th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:34)
    - Friday Dec 13th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:35)
    - Monday Dec 16th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:36)
    - Tuesday Dec 17th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:37)
    - Wednesday Dec 18th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:38)
    - Thursday Dec 19th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:39)
    - Monday Jan 6th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:40)
    - Tuesday Jan 7th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:41)
    - Wednesday Jan 18th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:42)
    - Thursday Jan 9th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:43)
    - Friday Jan 10th, 1963 (Box-folder 37:44)
    - Friday Jan 17th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:45)
    - Monday Jan 20th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:46)
    - Tuesday Jan 21st, 1964 (Box-folder 37:47)
    - Wednesday Jan 22nd, 1964 (Box-folder 37:48)
    - Thursday Jan 23rd, 1964 (Box-folder 37:49)
    - Friday Jan 24th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:50)
    - Monday Jan 27th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:51)
    - Tuesday Jan 28th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:52)
    - Wednesday Jan 29th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:53)
    - Cafeteria Daily Records Week Ending 9/20/1963-12/20/1963 (Box-folder 37:54)
    - Tuesday Feb 3rd, 1964 (Box-folder 37:55)
    - Wednesday Feb 4th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:56)
    - Thursday Feb 5th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:57)
    - Thursday Feb 6th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:58)
    - Friday Feb 7th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:59)
    - Monday Feb 10th, 1964 (Box-folder 37:60)
    - Tuesday Feb 11th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:1)
    - Thursday Feb 13th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:2)
    - Friday Feb 14th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:3)
    - Monday Feb 17th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:4)
    - Tuesday Feb 18th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:5)
    - Wednesday Feb 19, 1964 (Box-folder 38:6)
    - Thursday Feb 20th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:7)
    - Friday Feb 21st, 1964 (Box-folder 38:8)
    - Monday Feb 24th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:9)
    - Tuesday Feb 25th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:10)
    - Wednesday Feb 26th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:11)
    - Thursday Feb 27, 1964 (Box-folder 38:12)
    - Friday Feb 28th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:13)
    - Monday March 2nd, 1964 (Box-folder 38:14)
    - Tuesday March 3rd, 1964 (Box-folder 38:15)
    - Wednesday March 3rd, 1964 (Box-folder 38:16)
    - Thursday March 5th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:17)
    - Friday March 6th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:18)
    - Monday March 9th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:19)
    - Tuesday March 10th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:20)
    - Wednesday March 11th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:21)
    - Thursday March 12th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:22)
    - Friday MArch 13th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:23)
    - Monday March 16th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:24)
    - Tuesday March 17th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:25)
    - Wednesday March 18th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:26)
    - Thursday March 19th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:27)
    - Friday March 20th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:28)
    - Monday March 23rd, 1964 (Box-folder 38:29)
    - Tuesday March 24th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:30)
    - Wednesday March 25th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:31)
    - Thursday March 26th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:32)
    - Friday March 27th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:33)
    - Wednesday April 1st, 1964 (Box-folder 38:34)
    - Thursday April 2nd, 1964 (Box-folder 38:35)
    - Friday April 3rd, 1964 (Box-folder 38:36)
    - Monday April 6, 1964 (Box-folder 38:37)
    - Tuesday April 7, 1964 (Box-folder 38:38)
    - Wednesday April 8th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:39)
    - Thursday April 9th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:40)
    - Friday April 10th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:41)
    - Monday April 13th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:42)
    - Tuesday April 14, 1964 (Box-folder 38:43)
    - Wednesday April 15, 1964 (Box-folder 38:44)
    - Thursday April 16th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:45)
    - Friday April 17th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:46)
    - Monday April 20th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:47)
    - Tuesday April 21st, 1964 (Box-folder 38:48)
    - Wednesday April 22, 1964 (Box-folder 38:49)
    - Thursday April 23rd, 1964 (Box-folder 38:50)
    - Friday April 24th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:51)
    - Monday April 27th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:52)
    - Tuesday April 28th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:53)
    - Wednesday April 29th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:54)
    - Thursday April 30th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:55)
    - Friday May 1st, 1964 (Box-folder 38:56)
    - Monday May 4th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:57)
    - Tuesday May 5th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:58)
    - Wednesday May 6th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:59)
    - Thursday May 7th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:60)
    - Friday May 8th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:61)
    - Monday May 11th, 1964 (Box-folder 38:62)
    - Tuesday May 12th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:1)
    - Wednesday May 13th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:2)
    - Thursday May 14th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:3)
    - Friday May 15th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:4)
    - Monday May 18th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:5)
    - Tuesday May 19th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:6)
    - Wednesday May 20th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:7)
    - Thursday May 21st, 1964 (Box-folder 39:8)
    - Friday May 22nd, 1964 (Box-folder 39:9)
    - Monday May 25th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:10)
    - Tuesday May 26th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:11)
    - Wednesday May 27th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:12)
    - Thursday May 28th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:13)
    - Friday May 29th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:14)
    - Monday June 1st, 1964 (Box-folder 39:15)
    - Tuesday June 2nd, 1964 (Box-folder 39:16)
    - Wednesday June 3rd, 1964 (Box-folder 39:17)
    - Thursday June 4th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:18)
    - Friday June 6th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:19)
    - Monday June 8th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:20)
    - Tuesday June 9th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:21)
    - Wednesday June 10th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:22)
    - Thursday June 11th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:23)
    - Friday June 12th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:24)
    - Tuesday June 23rd, 1964 (Box-folder 39:25)
    - Wednesday June 24th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:26)
    - Thursday June 25th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:27)
    - Friday June 26th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:28)
    - Monday June 29th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:29)
    - Tuesday June 30th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:30)
    - Wednesday July 1st, 1964 (Box-folder 39:31)
    - Thursday July 2nd, 1964 (Box-folder 39:32)
    - Friday July 3rd, 1964 (Box-folder 39:33)
    - Monday July 6th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:34)
    - Tuesday July 7th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:35)
    - Wednesday July 8th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:36)
    - Thursday July 9th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:37)
    - Friday July 10th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:38)
    - Monday July 13th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:39)
    - Tuesday July 14th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:40)
    - Wednesday July 15th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:41)
    - Thursday July 16th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:42)
    - Friday July 17th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:43)
    - Monday July 20th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:44)
    - Tuesday July 21st, 1964 (Box-folder 39:45)
    - Wednesday July 22nd, 1964 (Box-folder 39:46)
    - Thursday July 23rd, 1964 (Box-folder 39:47)
    - Friday July 24th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:48)
    - Monday July 27th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:49)
    - Tuesday July 28th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:50)
    - Thursday July 29th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:51)
    - Thursday July 30th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:52)
    - Friday July 31st, 1964 (Box-folder 39:53)
    - Monday August 3rd, 1964 (Box-folder 39:54)
    - Tuesday August 4th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:55)
    - Wednesday August 5th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:56)
    - Thursday August 6th, 1964 (Box-folder 39:57)
    - Paychecks (Box-folder 39:58)
    - Free Lunch Students 1963 and No Date (Box-folder 40:1)
    - Free Lunch Students Summer Session 1964 (Box-folder 40:2)
    - Free Lunch Applications "A" (Box-folder 40:3)
    - Free Lunch Applications "A" (Box-folder 40:4)
    - Free Lunch Applications "B" (Box-folder 40:5)
    - Free Lunch Applications "B" (Box-folder 40:6)
    - Free Lunch Applications "C" (Box-folder 40:7)
    - Free Lunch Applications "C" (Box-folder 40:8)
    - Free Lunch Application "D" (Box-folder 40:9)
    - Free Lunch Students "E" (Box-folder 40:10)
    - Free Lunch Applications "F" (Box-folder 40:11)
    - Free Lunch Applications "G" (Box-folder 40:12)
    - Free Lunch Applications "H" (Box-folder 40:13)
    - Free Lunch Applications "H" (Box-folder 40:14)
    - Free Lunch Applications "H-I" (Box-folder 40:15)
    - Free Lunch Students "J" (Box-folder 41:1)
    - Free Lunch Applications "J" (Box-folder 41:2)
    - Free Lunch Applications "K-L" (Box-folder 41:3)
    - Free Lunch Applications "L" (Box-folder 41:4)
    - Free Lunch Applications "M" (Box-folder 41:5)
    - Free Lunch Applications "M" (Box-folder 41:6)
    - Free Lunch Applications "N-O" (Box-folder 41:7)
    - Free Lunch Application "P" (Box-folder 41:8)
    - Free Lunch Application "P" (Box-folder 41:9)
    - Free Lunch Applications "R" (Box-folder 41:10)
    - Free Lunch Applications "R" (Box-folder 41:11)
    - Free Lunch Applications "S" (Box-folder 41:12)
    - Free Lunch Applications "S" (Box-folder 41:13)
    - Free Lunch Applications "S" (Box-folder 41:14)
    - Free Lunch Applications "S" (Box-folder 41:15)
    - Free Lunch Applications "T" (Box-folder 41A:1)
    - Free Lunch Applications "T" (Box-folder 41A:2)
    - Free Lunch Applications "U" (Box-folder 41A:3)
    - Free Lunch Applications "V" (Box-folder 41A:4)
    - Free Lunch Applications "W" (Box-folder 41A:5)
    - Free Lunch Applications "W" (Box-folder 41A:6)
    - Free Lunch Applications "W" (Box-folder 41A:7)
    - Free Lunch Applications "W" (Box-folder 41A:8)
    - Free Lunch Applications "W" (Box-folder 41A:9)
  - Absentee Sheets
    - Absentee Sheets 3/10-4/10 (Box-folder 42:1)
    - Absentee Reports Prior to November 16th (Box-folder 42:2)
    - Absentee Reports Prior to October 15th (Box-folder 42:3)
    - Absentee Reports Prior to December 15th (Box-folder 42:4)
    - Absentee Report February 10th (Box-folder 42:5)
    - Absentee Reports April 10th-MAy 10th (Box-folder 42:6)
    - Absentee Reports 5/10-6/10 (Box-folder 42:7)
    - Teachers Summer Session (Box-folder 42:8)
    - Absentees Summer Session (Box-folder 42:9)
    - Check Out Sheets and Summer Sessions (Box-folder 42:10)
    - Final Check Out Sheets (Box-folder 42:11)
    - Absentee Reports Prior to Jan 15th (Box-folder 42:12)
    - Contacts (Box-folder 42:13)
    - Active Medical Services (Box-folder 42:14)
    - Attendance (Box-folder 42:15)
    - Absentee Report (Box-folder 42:16)
    - Bus Repairs Needed (Box-folder 42:17)
    - School Car Mileage Report (Box-folder 42:18)
  - School Attendance
    list of each student's attendance. These were required statistics maintained for the state.
    - School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43:1)
    - School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43:2)
    - School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43:3)
    - School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43:4)
    - School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43:5)
    - School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43:6)
    - School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43:7)
    - School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43:8)
    - School Attendance (Box-folder 43:9)
    - School Attendance (Box-folder 43:10)
    - School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43:11)
    - School Attendance (Box-folder 43:12)
    - School Attendance (Box-folder 43:13)
    - School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 43:14)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:1)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:2)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:3)
    - Prince Edward Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:4)
    - Prince Edward Attendance (Box-folder 44:5)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance (Box-folder 44:6)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:7)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance (Box-folder 44:8)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:9)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:10)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:11)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:12)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:13)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:14)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:15)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:16)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:17)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:18)
    - Prince Edward School Attendance (Box-folder 44:19)
    - Annual Report 1962 (Box-folder 44:20)
    - Schedule of Afternoon Activities 1963-1964 (Box-folder 44:21)
    - Daily Attendance Sept-Oct 1963 (Box-folder 45:1)
    - Daily Attendance Nov-Dec 1963 (Box-folder 45:2)
    - Daily Attendance January 1964 (Box-folder 45:3)
    - Daily Attendance February 1964 (Box-folder 45:4)
    - Daily Attendance March 1964 (Box-folder 45:5)
    - Daily Attendance April 1964 (Box-folder 45:6)
    - Daily Attendance May 1964 (Box-folder 45:7)
    - Daily Attendance (Saturdays) Jan-May 1964 (Box-folder 45:8)
    - School Membership 1964 (Box-folder 45:9)
    - Dentists 1964 (Box-folder 45:10)
    - Recreational 1964 (Box-folder 45:11)
    - Daily Attendance Report (Summer Session) 1964 (Box-folder 45:12)
    - Field Trips (Box-folder 45:13)
    - Safety Patrol (Box-folder 45:14)
    - Notes: Parents, Teachers, Doctors (Box-folder 45:15)
    - Grading Scale, Grade Placement 1963-1965 (Box-folder 45:16)
    - The Program of Studies (Box-folder 45:17)
    - Vocational Training Center 1964 (Box-folder 45:18)
    - Referrals for Absentee Children 1964 (Box-folder 45:19)
    - Drop Outs (Box-folder 45:20)
  - Monthly Reports
    Required by the state of Virginia. Average daily attendance and absentees.
    - Prince Edward Free School Association Special Reports 1963-1964 (Box-folder 46:1)
    - Teachers Monthly Reports 1963-1964 (Box-folder 46:2)
    - Procter and Gamble (Box-folder 46:3)
    - Requisitions Jan-June 1964 (Box-folder 46:4)
    - Monthly Reports Branch #1 Oct 1963-Jan 1964 (Box-folder 46:5)
    - Monthly Reports Branch #1 Oct 1963- March 1964 (Box-folder 46:6)
    - Monthly Reports Branch # 1 April-June 1964 (Box-folder 46:7)
    - Monthly Reports # 2 Jan-June 1964 (Box-folder 46:8)
    - Monthly Reports September 1963 (Box-folder 46:9)
    - Monthly Reports October 1963 (Box-folder 46:10)
    - Monthly Reports November 1963 (Box-folder 46:11)
    - Monthly Reports December 1963 (Box-folder 46:12)
    - Monthly Reports Jan 1964 (Box-folder 46:13)
    - Monthly Reports February 1964 (Box-folder 46:14)
    - Monthly Reports March 1964 (Box-folder 46:15)
    - Monthly Reports April 1964 (Box-folder 46:16)
    - Monthly Reports May 1964 (Box-folder 46:17)
    - Monthly Reports June 1964 (Box-folder 46:18)
  - Transportation
    It was estimated that over 1,000 students would need transportation to and from school each day. Included in this sub-series are: bus drivers reports, maintenance records.
    - Reports of Pupils Transported Feb 1963-Jan 1964 (Box-folder 47:1)
    - Reports of Pupil Transported Feb 1964- July 1964 (Box-folder 47:2)
    - Report of Pupils Transported Sept 1963-March 1964 (Box-folder 47:3)
    - Reports of Pupils Transported Dec 1963- March 1964 (Box-folder 47:4)
    - Reports of Pupils Transported Sept 1963- may 1964 (Box-folder 47:5)
    - Reports of Pupils Transported R.R. Moton (Box-folder 47:6)
    - Reports of Pupils Transported (Box-folder 47:7)
  - Special Education
    Primarily test scores used to place students in Special Education Courses. Arranged by grade and alphabetically.
    - Students Recommended for Special Education 1964 (Box-folder 47:8)
    - Test Forms Age 6 (Box-folder 47:9)
    - Test Forms age 7 A-P (Box-folder 47:10)
    - Test Forms age 7 R-W (Box-folder 47:11)
    - Test Forms Age 8 (Box-folder 47:12)
    - Test Forms age 9 A-Q (Box-folder 47:13)
    - Test Forms age 9 N-W (Box-folder 47:14)
    - Test Forms age 10 (Box-folder 47:15)
    - Test Forms age 11 (Box-folder 47:16)
    - Prince Edward County List of Student drop outs and absentee (Box-folder 47:17)
    - Prince Edward County List of Student Drop Outs and Absentee 1963-1964 (Box-folder 47:18)
    - Applications by Alphabet: A (Box-folder 48:1)
    - Applications by Alphabet: B (Box-folder 48:2)
    - Applications by Alphabet: C (Box-folder 48:3)
    - Applications by Alphabet: D (Box-folder 48:4)
    - Applications by Alphabet: E (Box-folder 48:5)
    - Applications by Alphabet: F (Box-folder 48:6)
    - Applications by Alphabet: G (Box-folder 48:7)
    - Applications by Alphabet: H (Box-folder 48:8)
    - Applications by Alphabet: J (Box-folder 48:9)
    - Applications by Alphabet: M (Box-folder 48:10)
    - Applications by Alphabet: O (Box-folder 48:11)
    - Applications by Alphabet: P (Box-folder 48:12)
    - Applications by Alphabet: R (Box-folder 48:13)
    - Applications by Alphabet: S (Box-folder 48:14)
    - Applications by Alphabet: T (Box-folder 48:15)
    - Applications by Alphabet: W (Box-folder 48:16)
    - Applications by Alphabet: A 48:17 (Box-folder 48:17)
- Teachers Records
  Four years without a public education system devastated the African American school aged population. In order to asset the damage and effect some change the office of Pupil Personnel Services was established. The director of Pupil Personnel Services coordinated the following departments: Guidance, Health, Psychological and social work services.
  - Grade Sheets
    Final grade sheets from the Prince Edward County Free School teaching faculty. Restricted
    - Daily Roll (Box-folder 49:1)
    - Grade Sheet Connelly (Box-folder 49:2)
    - Grade Sheet Cuffee (Box-folder 49:3)
    - Grade Sheets Forest (Box-folder 49:4)
    - Grade Sheet Hosley (Box-folder 49:5)
    - Grade Sheet Jones, D (Box-folder 49:6)
    - Grade Sheet Jones (Box-folder 49:7)
    - Grade Sheet Johnson, C.W. (Box-folder 49:8)
    - Grade Sheets Johnson, H.C. (Box-folder 49:9)
    - Grade Sheet Parker (Box-folder 49:10)
    - Grade Sheet Franklin (Box-folder 49:11)
    - Grade Sheet Ms. Pollard (Box-folder 49:12)
    - Grade Sheet Ms. Munson (Box-folder 49:13)
    - Grade Sheet DeMoss (Box-folder 49:14)
    - Lemuel Bland (Box-folder 49:15)
    - Grade Sheet Lyle (Box-folder 49:16)
    - Morgan (Box-folder 49:17)
    - Grade Sheets Saunders J.A. (Box-folder 49:18)
    - Grade Sheets Taylor (Box-folder 49:19)
    - H.L. Watson (Box-folder 49:20)
    - Whelhel (Box-folder 49:21)
    - Weitzenfold, J.S. (Box-folder 49:22)
    - Whitaker (Box-folder 49:23)
    - Mrs. Williams (Box-folder 49:24)
    - Van Bans Grade Sheets (Box-folder 49:25)
  - Grade Books
    Grade books maintained by the teaching faculty of the Prince Edward Free School Association. Restricted
    - Grade Books (Box 50-52)
  - Text Books
    Book files used by the teachers in the Free School. There are also included list of recommended books for certain subjects. Arranged by grade level.
    - Books:Recommended for Home Economics Education (Box-folder 53:1)
    - Books: Grade 7 (Box-folder 53:2)
    - Books: Grade 8 (Box-folder 53:3)
    - Books: Grade 10 (Box-folder 53:4)
    - Books: Grade 12 (Box-folder 53:5)
    - Books: Grade 12 (Box-folder 53:6)
  - Summer Session
    The schools and grounds were made available for students to use during the summer months when they were not in school. This sub-series documents those people who were assigned or agreed to work as supervisors for this program.
    - Summer Session Worsham (Box-folder 53:7)
    - Summer Recreation Schedule Worsham (Box-folder 53:8)
    - Summer Recreation Schedule (Box-folder 53:9)
    - Summer Recreational Schedule Worsham (Box-folder 53:10)
    - Summer Recreation Worsham (Box-folder 53:11)
    - Summer Recreation Schedule Worsham (Box-folder 53:12)
    - Summer Recreation Schedule Worsham (Box-folder 53:13)
    - Summer Recreation Schedule Worsham (Box-folder 53:14)
    - Summer Recreation Schedule Worsham (Box-folder 53:15)
    - Summer Recreation Schedule Worsham (Box-folder 53:16)
    - Summer Recreation Schedule Worsham (Box-folder 53:17)
    - Summer Recreation Schedule Worsham (Box-folder 53:18)
    - Summer Recreation Schedule Worsham (Box-folder 53:19)
- Student Records
  - Pupil Registration Cards, Name, age, and addresses of the students who registered for the Free School in September 1963.Restricted (Box 54-59)
    Alphabetically
  - Standardized Test (Box 63-106)